

Summary

I am a full-stack developer with a management background. I have completed a diploma in Full-Stack Web Development and have 4 years of experience in customer service and management. I found myself consumed with all things related to programming and I am currently focused on developing full-stack coding skills and pursuing my passion for software development. I am eager to collaborate with my coding skills.

Employment

Freelance Ottawa
Dec. 2021 to Current

Developing website with react.js as frontend and java spring-boot, MySQL as backend. My role involves developing and testing the react frontend. Experience using Jira, git, and confluence.

Hinduja Global Solution Pvt Ltd

Customer Service Advisor

Ottawa, ON Mar. 2021 to Sept. 2021

- Customer support skill
- Demonstrated attention to detail, flexibility, and initiative
- Professional handling interactions with customers in a polite and courteous manner
- Accurate keyboarding and data entry skills

E-Web Guru Solution Pvt Itd

HR Executive/ Generalist

Noida, India Mar. 2014 to Sept. 2018

- Strong written and oral communication skills, diplomacy, and professionalism
- Strong organizational and time management skills
- A good learner, ability to take initiative and prioritize workload
- Ability to work under pressure
- Experience in event planning
- Good analytical and decision making skills
- A good team player is able to work independently and as a team in a fast-paced environment.
- Excellent interpersonal and Customer Relationship skills

Projects

Yelp_like 2021 to 2021

Restaurant Reviews app. Tech Stack: Ruby, Rails, Javascript, React and CSS

Tiny App 2021 to 2021

RESTful URL Shortening service.

Tech Stack: Express, Node

Tweeter 2021 to 2021

Twitter clone powered by AJAX.

Tech Stack: Express, jQuery, MongoDB, Node

Scheduler 2021 to 2021

React based project to create meetings for students to connect with mentors in real-time. Tech Stack: React, Axios, Classnames, Normalize, Storybook

Quiz App 2021 to 2021

users can create quizzes

users can make their quiz unlisted (make them private and not available on the home page, but if someone knows the quiz URL they can visit and take the quiz)

Contact

navyasrajput@gmail.com

4 6135014556

♀ Ottawa. ON

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/navyarajput-9627aa165

nrajput-github

Education

Lighthouse Lab, Ottawa, ON, Canada Sept. 2021 to Dec. 2021

Diploma Full Stack Web Development 2021

IVWI I University India 2010 to

JVWU University India 2010 to 2012

Master of Business Administration

Skills

LANGUAGES/LIBRARIES/FRAMEWORKS:

Javascript

HTML SOL

CSS

Ruby

NodeJS

ReactJS

Express.js

Rails

JQuery

Ajax

Redux

Saas

Bootstrap Jira

JSON

DATABASES:

PostgreSQL